{
    "subject": "resource/Geoff_Love",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Pop_music",
    "human_readable": "Geoff Love is a musician who works in Pop music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.967253565788269,
            "question": "Does Geoff Love work in the Pop music genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9558100700378418,
            "question": "Is Geoff Love a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.895626425743103,
            "question": "Name a musician who works in Pop music."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8411603569984436,
            "question": "Who is Geoff Love?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273414969444275,
            "question": "What genre of music does Geoff Love perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.762884795665741,
            "question": "What kind of music does Geoff Love create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.592408299446106,
            "question": "What is Geoff Love's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5052746534347534,
            "question": "Who is known for performing in the Pop genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4962746500968933,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a musician who plays Pop music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42592597007751465,
            "question": "What is the name of the musician known for Pop music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Geoff Love is a musician who works in Pop music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5843_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a musician who plays Pop music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5843_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known for performing in the Pop genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5843_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Geoff Love's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5843_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5843_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Geoff Love is a musician who works in pop music. This can be derived from multiple sources within the documents, including his work as an arranger and composer of easy listening and pop versions of film themes, performing under the pseudonym Manuel and The Music of The Mountains."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}